ACTWU's Organizing Department Records. 5619/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Ronald Harris, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- Tom Hummel, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 12)
- Virginia Keyer, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 13)
- Trudy J. Khan, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 14)
- Donna Krenik, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 15)
- Bessie Manning, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 16)
- Wallace McMullen, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 17)
- Anthony Miceli, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 18)
- Ray Mullins, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 19)
- John Notarangelo, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 20)
- Erika Outland, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 21)
- Maurice Robillard, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 22)
- Harold Bagwell, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 23)
- John Barry, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 24)
- Diane Bruneau, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 25)
- Ron Harris, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 26)
- Tom Hummel, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 27)
- Anthony Miceli, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 28)
- Ray Mullins, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 29)
- John Notarangelo, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 30)
- James Orange, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 31)
- Maurice Robillard, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 32)
- Carol Sheerer, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 33)
- Alice York, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 34)
- Sidney Young, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 35)
- Harold Bagwell, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 36)
- John Barry, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 37)
- Diane Bruneau, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 38)
- Pat Cronin, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 39)
- Ronald Harris, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 40)
- Thomas Hummel, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 41)
- Trudye Khan, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 42)
- Mary Ellen Koval, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 43)
- Virginia Keyser, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 44)
- Donna Krenik, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 45)
- Anthony Miceli, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 46)
- Ray Mullins, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 47)
- John Notarangelo, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 48)
- Erika Outland, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 49)
- James Orange, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 50)
- David Rathke, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 51)
- Maurice Robillard, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 52)
- Mtg. Committee on Organization, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  Marh 28th
- Organizer's Handbook (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Weekly Organizing Activity Reports, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Weekly Organizing Activity Reports, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Weekly Organizing Activity Reports, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Data on Organizing, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Propaganda and Membership Info (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Bi-Weekly Organizing Activity Reports, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- International Woodworkers. Summary of Comments from Farkas, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- ACTWU Organizer Information [folder 1 of 2], 1982 (Box 95, Folder 10)
- ACTWU Organizer Information [folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 95, Folder 11)
- Stevens Info (Box 95, Folder 12)
- Union, Textile, and ACTWU, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 13)
- ACTWU Organizer Book [folder 1 of 3], 1982 (Box 95, Folder 14)
- ACTWU Organizer [folder 2 of 3], 1982 (Box 95, Folder 15)
- ACTWU Organizer [folder 3 of 3], 1982 (Box 95, Folder 16)
- AFL- CIO Documents, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 17)
- Staff Conference. Developing an In-house Polling Program, 1980-1982 (Box 95, Folder 18)
- The Stevens Worker, 1978-1979 (Box 95, Folder 19)
- Organizer's Source Book (Box 95, Folder 20)
- ACTWU Documents [folder 1 of 2], 1981 (Box 95, Folder 21)
- ACTWU Documents [folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 95, Folder 22)
- AFL- CIO NLRB Election Summary, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 23)
- Teamsters on Fall River, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Teamsters Union, 1980-1982 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Wage Guide Lines, 1979 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Wage Rates in Textiles, 1967-1977 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- Warner Bros, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- New Worker to Worker Program, 1978-1979 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Worker to Worker Bulletin, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Threads, 1979 (Box 96, Folder 8)
- TWUA Health Plan, 1981-1982 (Box 96, Folder 9)
- Trade Readjustment Allowance, 1979 (Box 96, Folder 10)
- Textile World, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 11)
- Union Label Materials, 1966-1981 (Box 96, Folder 12)
- University of Wisconsin, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 13)
- United Furniture Workers, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 14)
- Annual Reports. United Labor Service Agency, 1978-1981 (Box 96, Folder 15)
- United Food and Commercial Workers, 1980-1981 (Box 96, Folder 16)
- University of Toronto, 1977-1979 (Box 96, Folder 17)
- United Rubber Workers, 1969-1981 (Box 96, Folder 18)
- United Steelworkers and ACTWU Jurisdiction, 1979 (Box 96, Folder 19)
- United Steelworkers, 1970-1981 (Box 96, Folder 20)
- Unorganized Plants, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 21)
- Oral History Project, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 22)
- T- Shirts, 1972-1978 (Box 96, Folder 23)
- Paul Swaity, 1980-1983 (Box 96, Folder 24)
- Paul Swaity, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 25)
- Strikes, 1978-1979 (Box 96, Folder 26)
- How to Conduct Strikes, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 27)
- Financial Data, 1982-1983 (Box 96, Folder 28)
- Solidarity Day Trip to Washington D. C., 1981 (Box 96, Folder 29)
- Southern Wage Drive, 1975-1978 (Box 96, Folder 30)
- Southern Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 31)
- Senior Citizens, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 32)
- Jacob Sheinkman, 1978-1983 (Box 96, Folder 33)
- The Church's Responsibility in the Changing Southern Economy, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 34)
- Southerners for Economic Justice, 1976-1978 (Box 96, Folder 35)
- J. P. Stevens: Southerners for Economic Justice [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1981 (Box 96, Folder 36)
- J. P. Stevens: Southerners for Economic Justice [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1981 (Box 96, Folder 37)
- Textile Industry History, 1976-1978 (Box 96, Folder 38)
- Quin, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- George Dion and John Notarangelo, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- C. Bush and T. Hummel, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 3)
- R. Mullins. L. A. Dunigan. C. Hawkins. V. Keyser, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- O. Anania. J. Harrison. E. Sherman, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Harold Beck. Thiokol. William Graham, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Harold Bagwell. R. Freeman. E. Hamilton. V. Keyser, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- J. Walraven. W. South. T. Barker. G. Brown. C. Farris, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- Activity Reports: Delinquent, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 9)
- R. Charland. W. Clark. M. Robillard, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 10)
- J. Barry. M. Black. J. Craven. H. Mann, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 11)
- P. Pope. F. Nye. T. Misiaszek, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 12)
- E. Blackwelde. N. Bresciani. R. Dove. W. Cannon, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 13)
- Anti-Union Propaganda, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 14)
- Intelligence for Targeting (Box 97, Folder 15)
- Union Information (Box 97, Folder 16)
- Union Information. Labor Law (Box 97, Folder 17)
- Mid-West Weekly Organizing Activity Reports, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- "right-to-work" laws correspondence, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Fact Power, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- B. Bozman. S. Sachen. J. Whitely, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Quin State. R. Manini. McCauley. G. Mikola, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Quin State. R. Mullins. J. Whitely. P. Ventura, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Correspondence. Misc. Documents, 1979 (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Cards with California ACTWU Stores except for L. A. and Orange County (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Alphabetically Organized Cards with California Stores (Box 98, Folder 9)
- New Hampshire Store Cards (Box 98, Folder 10)
- Connecticut Store Cards (Box 98, Folder 11)
- Maine Store Cards (Box 98, Folder 12)
- Vermont and Rhode Island Store Cards (Box 98, Folder 13)
- Massachusetts Store Cards. (Box 98, Folder 14)
  Barnstable, Berkshire and Bristol Counties
- Massachusetts Store Cards (Box 98, Folder 15)
  Essex, Franklin, Hampden, and Hampshire
- Massachusetts Store Cards (Box 98, Folder 16)
  Middlesex, Nantucket, Norfolk, and Plymouth
- Massachusetts Store Cards (Box 98, Folder 17)
  Suffolk and Worcester Counties
- Textile. IUD (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Southern Textile, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Wage Agitation Conference, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Southern Wage Drive, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Figures for Paul Swaity, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Southern Wage Drive Conference, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- Mid-South Regional Conference, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Union Info, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Wage Raise Propaganda. Hand Written Notes, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 9)
- J. P.S. Update, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 10)
- Textile Week. Newspaper Clippings, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 11)
- Resolutions (Box 99, Folder 12)
- Union Organization. Apparel Division Institutes. George Meany, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 13)
- AFL- CIO Documents, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 14)
- How to Organize a Union in your Plant (Box 99, Folder 15)
- Misc. Notes. Union Organizing Documents (Box 99, Folder 16)
- Threads (Box 99, Folder 17)
- Convention. Resolutions, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 18)
- IUD Conventions, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 19)
- Resolutions, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 20)
- Organizing Campaign. Resolution, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 21)
- TWUA. Resolutions., 1975-1977 (Box 99, Folder 22)
- J. P. Stevens. Resolutions, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 23)
- Organizing Progress, 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 24)
- Correspondence regarding various companies, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 25)
- Fabric Companies, 1978-1979 (Box 99, Folder 26)
- Key Competitive Plants, 1978-1979 (Box 99, Folder 27)
- Companies, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 28)
- Mid-West Unorganized Plants, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 29)
- South Unorganized Plants, 1970 (Box 99, Folder 30)
- Far West Unorganized Plants, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 31)
- Financial Information. Newspaper Clippings, 1976-1980 (Box 99, Folder 32)
- Upper South Unorganized Plants (Box 99, Folder 33)
- Textile Workers Union of America (Box 99, Folder 34)
- TWUA Plants (Box 99, Folder 35)
- Far West TWUA Plants, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 36)
- Textile Division Information, 1977-1980 (Box 99, Folder 37)
- TWUA, 1971-1972 (Box 99, Folder 38)
- TWUA Plants and Targets, 1978-1980 (Box 99, Folder 39)
- Southern Companies (Box 99, Folder 40)
- North Carolina Plants (Box 99, Folder 41)
- California, Canada, Oregon, and Colorado Plants (Box 99, Folder 42)
- New Jersey, Kentucky and Georgia (Box 99, Folder 43)
- Vermont, Tennessee, Illinois, Pennsylvania, and Massachusetts (Box 99, Folder 44)
- Wisconsin, Minnesota, Kansas, Washington, Rhode Island, and Connecticut (Box 99, Folder 45)
- New York, Texas, Tennessee, Michigan, Ohio, Maine, North Carolina, New Hampshire, Alabama, and Mississippi (Box 99, Folder 46)
- Activity Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Off Payroll [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 100, Folder 2)
- Report on General Executive Board, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Fact Power. Management Campaigns. Hearings, 1978-1980 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Off Payroll, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- New England. Synthetic (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Branch Plants of Companies with ACTWU Contracts, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 7)
- Fact Power, 1973-1981 (Box 100, Folder 8)
- Staff Manual (Box 100, Folder 9)
- Misc. Documents. Fact Power. [folder 1 of 3], 1964-1981 (Box 100, Folder 10)
- Misc. Documents. Fact Power. [folder 2 of 3], 1964-1981 (Box 100, Folder 11)
- Misc. Documents. Fact Power [folder 3 of 3], 1964-1981 (Box 100, Folder 12)
- Unorganized Target Plants. New England (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Unorganized Apparel Plants, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Companies (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Companies (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Pennsylvania ACTWU Organizing Targets (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Pennsylvania Plants. Misc. Forms, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Pennsylvania Directory of Apparel Targets, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Unorganized Plants, 1981 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  Georgia, Alabama, Tennessee, Louisiana, Virginia
- Unorganized Targets. New England [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- Unorganized Targets. New England [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 101, Folder 10)
- Maps. Surveys of Unorganized Target Plants [folder 1 of 2] (Box 101, Folder 11)
- Maps. Surveys of Unorganized Target Plants [folder 2 of 2] (Box 101, Folder 12)
- Organizing Project (A-I), 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 13)
- Organizing Project (J-Z), 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 14)
- Organizing Targets. Chicago Area, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 15)
- Textile Apparel Targets, 1981 (Box 101, Folder 16)
- Daily News Records, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 17)
- Survey of Unorganized Target Plants (Box 101, Folder 18)
- Textile Targets: Alabama, 1974-1979 (Box 101, Folder 19)
- NLRB Election Histories, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 20)
- Mid-West Upper South, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Convention Committees, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- A Workers' Guide to Labor Law. Organize Union, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- J. P. Stevens [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 102, Folder 4)
- J. P. Stevens [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 102, Folder 5)
- J. P. Stevens, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- New York, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- New England and Synthetics, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 8)
- New England and Synthetics, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 9)
- Off Payroll, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 10)
- Activity Reports, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 11)
- Deep South [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 102, Folder 12)
- Deep South [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 102, Folder 13)
- Quin [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 102, Folder 14)
- Quin [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 102, Folder 15)
- Upper South and Mid West, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 16)
- Canada, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 17)
- Coordinator Seminar, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- 2 Day Seminar, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 2)
- Union Fine Legal (Box 103, Folder 3)
  Overhead Slide
- Consultant Reports, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Proposal for an Employer Consultant's Project, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- Kayser Roth, 1980-1981 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  Allendale, South Carolina
- Kayser Roth Union Leaflets, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- ACTWU Reports and Literature, 1981-1982 (Box 103, Folder 8)
- ACTWU Sale Knitting, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 9)
- Neutrality Cases, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 10)
- Seminar for Regional Organizing Coordinators, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 11)
- National Organizing Coordinating, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 12)
- Company Anti Union Tactics, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 13)
- ACTWU Report, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 14)
- Employer Anti-Union Consultants, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 15)
- Company and Union Activity, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 16)
- Committee on Organization, 1980-1981 (Box 103, Folder 17)
- Legal. Consultants, 1978-1980 (Box 103, Folder 18)
- Union Activity, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 19)
- ACTWU, 1980-1982 (Box 103, Folder 20)
- Kayser Roth, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 21)
- Materials Distributed to the Committee, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Seminar on Employer Anti-Union Consultants, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Union Information and Documents, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Management Campaign. Organizing Conference, 1979-1981 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- National Coordinated Organizing Campaign, 1978-1979 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- Consultants. Wage Information, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 6)
- Executive Organizing Mtg., 1984 (Box 104, Folder 7)
- Executive Organizing Strategy, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- Meeting with Southern Directors, 1983-1984 (Box 104, Folder 9)
- Executive Organizing Discussions, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 10)
- Attendees to Union Busting Seminar, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO National/Coordinated Organizing Committee, 1977-1983 (Box 104, Folder 12)
- ACTWU. Textiles, 1982-1983 (Box 104, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO, 1980-1982 (Box 104, Folder 14)
- ACTWU. AFL-CIO, 1978-1983 (Box 104, Folder 15)
- AFL- CIO, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 16)
- Organizing Committee Mtg., 1985 (Box 104, Folder 17)
- Executive Organizing Meeting, 1984-1985 (Box 104, Folder 18)
- New England Organizing, 1976-1978 (Box 104, Folder 19)
- Organizing Targets. Rhode Island (Box 104, Folder 20)
- ACTWU New England (Box 104, Folder 21)
- Dyeing and Finishing Organizing Project, 1976-1977 (Box 104, Folder 22)
- Mississippi AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 23)
- Textile and Clothing Organizing Targets, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 24)
  West Virginia
- Organizing Targets. Canada, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 25)
- Johnson and Johnson, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 26)
  Winnipeg
- Organizing Targets. Upper South (Box 104, Folder 27)
- Organizing Targets. Mid-West, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 28)
- Organizing Targets. New York City, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 29)
- Organizing Targets. South, 1970-1976 (Box 104, Folder 30)
- ACTWU: Organized Knit Product Plants, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 31)
- Kayser-Roth. Tupperware, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 32)
- Research Assistance to Organizing, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 33)
- Organizing Dept. J. P. Stevens Campaign, 1976-1977 (Box 104, Folder 34)
- J. P. Stevens Organizing, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 35)
- Boycott Sponsors. Organizing Campaign, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 36)
- Policy on Organizing Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 104, Folder 37)
- J. P. Stevens. Textile Union, 1975-1977 (Box 104, Folder 38)
- Campaign Guide. Resolutions (Box 104, Folder 39)
- J. P. Stevens, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 40)
- Staff Assignments, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 41)
- NLRB. J. P. Stevens, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 42)
- J. P. Stevens Workers, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 43)
- J. P. Stevens Committee, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 44)
- New England Information, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 45)
- New England Documents, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 46)
- Threads, 1976-1977 (Box 104, Folder 47)
- Information about Targets, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Organized I. L.G.W.U. Shops, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Pennsylvania, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Pennsylvania Targets, 1977-1980 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- NLRB. ACTWU. Research Dept, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Apparel and Textile, 1971-1979 (Box 105, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Apparel and Textile, 1966-1976 (Box 105, Folder 7)
- J. P. Stevens Loses Again (Box 105, Folder 8)
- NLRB. ACTWU Research Dept., 1980-1982 (Box 105, Folder 9)
- J. P. Stevens (Box 105, Folder 10)
- Orientation Kit. J. P. Stevens Campaign [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1976 (Box 105, Folder 11)
- Orientation Kit for New Staff Representatives. A guide book for Union Organizers, 1961-1977 (Box 105, Folder 12)
- Orientation Kit for New Staff Representatives, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 13)
- J. P. Stevens Leadership Mtg., 1977 (Box 105, Folder 14)
- ACTWU. AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 15)
- Stevens Latest Programs, 1976-1977 (Box 105, Folder 16)
- J. P. Stevens Organizing Programs, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 17)
- Labor Informative Documents (Box 105, Folder 18)
- J. P. Stevens Organizing, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 19)
- ACTWU Members Kit and J. P. Stevens, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 20)
- ACTWU. J. P. Stevens, 1976-1978 (Box 105, Folder 21)
- ACTWU Dept. Heads Mtg., 1977 (Box 105, Folder 22)
- AFL- CIO. Textile Workers Union, 1975-1976 (Box 105, Folder 23)
- Textile Workers Union of America (Box 105, Folder 24)
- NLRB. J. P. Stevens (Box 105, Folder 25)
- ACTWU Documents, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 26)
- New England Apparel Firms [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1978 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- New England Apparel Firms [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1978 (Box 106, Folder 2)
- Survey of Unorganized Target Plants (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Organized ACTWU Plants, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Pennsylvania Organizing Drive, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Unorganized Apparel and Textile Plants. Pennsylvania [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 106, Folder 6)
- Unorganized Apparel and Textile Plants. Pennsylvania [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 106, Folder 7)
- ACTWU Information, 1982 (Box 106, Folder 8)
- Research Information on Organizational Targets, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 9)
- Master List of Unorganized Plants, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 10)
- Pennsylvania Organizing Progress, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 11)
- Hanes. Yocom Knitting Co., 1982 (Box 107, Folder 11)
- Joyce Miller. Newspaper clippings, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 12)
- Hanes Corp Misc., 1979-1983 (Box 107, Folder 13)
- Hanes Principles (Box 107, Folder 14)
- Hanes. Research Dept. Memos, 1982-1983 (Box 107, Folder 15)
- Hanes. Women's Issues, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 16)
- Hanes. Worker's Compensation, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 17)
- Hanes Videotape, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 18)
- Hanes Video Tapes. General, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 19)
- Hanes. Women Against Pornography, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 20)
- Hanes. Video Program, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 21)
- Hanes Project Mtg., 1983 (Box 107, Folder 22)
- Hanes Executive Staff Mtg., 1983 (Box 107, Folder 23)
- Hanes Staff Mtg., 1981 (Box 107, Folder 24)
- Trip to Charlotte, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 25)
- Hanes Citizens Commission on Justice, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 26)
- Hanes Staff Mtg., 1983 (Box 107, Folder 27)
- Hanes Staff Conference, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 28)
- Hanes Executive Staff Meeting, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 29)
- Hanes Project, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 30)
- Hanes Strategy Meeting, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 31)
- Hanes (Consolidated Foods), 1982 (Box 107, Folder 32)
- Hanes Shareholders Meeting, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 33)
- Hanes Executive Staff Meeting, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 34)
- Hanes Phase 2, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 35)
- Meeting with Sheinkman and Brandon, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 36)
- Meeting with J. Sheinkman, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 37)
- Hanes. Executive Staff, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 38)
- Hanes Staff Conference, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 39)
- Hanes Operating Committee, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 40)
- Hanes. The Media, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 41)
- Hanes. Medical Plan, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 42)
- Hanes. Medical Task Force, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 43)
- Hanes. Clippings, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 44)
- Hanes. Nader's Letter, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 45)
- OSHA Fine of $100, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 46)
- Hanes OSHA/Hanes, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 47)
- Hanes. Puerto Rico, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 48)
- Hanes. Research Dept. Memos, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 49)
- Hanes Research Dept. Memos, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 50)
- Hanes. Research Dept. Memos, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 51)
- Hanes. Supporters of Corporative Responsibilities, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 52)
- Hanes. N.O.W. National Organization of Women, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 53)
- Hanes. Save-A-Stop, 1982-1983 (Box 107, Folder 54)
- Hanes. Shareholders Report, 1978-1983 (Box 107, Folder 55)
- Hanes Shareholders Mtg, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 56)
- Hanes. Jack Sheinkman, 1981-1984 (Box 107, Folder 57)
- Hanes Expense Reports, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 58)
- Hanes. Standard Meat Co., 1983 (Box 107, Folder 59)
- Hanes. CLWU Letter from J. Miller, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 60)
- Hanes. Connective Ministry Across the South, 1982-1983 (Box 107, Folder 61)
- Hanes. Robin Tallon, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 62)
- AFL- CIO. Hanes, 1983-1984 (Box 107, Folder 63)
- Southern Exposure, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 64)
- Consolidated Foods Corporation, 1978 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Hanes. AFL- CIO Report on CFC, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Hanes. CFC Officers, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 3)
- Hanes Project., 1982-1983 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- Hanes. Chicago Fed. Of Labor, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Hanes. CFC Earnings, 1979-1983 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- Hanes/CFC. Food and Beverage Trades Dept., 1980 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Hanes. CFC Letters to Employees, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 8)
- Hanes. CFC Research Study, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 9)
- Hanes. Corporate Strategies, 1982-1983 (Box 108, Folder 10)
- 8 facts Women should know about Consolidated Foods Corp., 1982-1983 (Box 108, Folder 11)
- Hanes Clippings, 1980-1983 (Box 108, Folder 12)
- Hanes. Gary W. Carrico, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 13)
- Hanes- Consolidated Foods, 1982-1983 (Box 108, Folder 14)
- Hanes. Pete Brandon, 1981-1984 (Box 108, Folder 15)
- Hanes. Brandon's Hanes Project Proposal, 1981-1983 (Box 108, Folder 16)
- Hanes Project. Brandon's Final, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 17)
- Hanes. Bob Bussel, 1982-1983 (Box 108, Folder 18)
- Hanes. Listing of Folders, 1981-1983 (Box 108, Folder 19)
- Hanes. Anti-Union Items, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 20)
- Hanes. ACTWU Press Releases, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 21)
- Hanes. Continental Illinois National Banking and Trust Co. of Chicago, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 22)
- Hanes First National Bank of Chicago, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 23)
- Hanes. Burt Beck, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 24)
- Hanes Staff Assignments, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 25)
- ACTWU and Hanes, 1981-1983 (Box 108, Folder 26)
- Arther Loevy, 1982-1983 (Box 108, Folder 27)
- L'Eggs Plant, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 28)
- L'Eggs Marketing Analysis, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 29)
- L'Eggs Clippings, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 30)
- Hanes Project Bills, 1978-1983 (Box 108, Folder 31)
- Hanes. Legal Matters, 1981-1982 (Box 108, Folder 32)
- Social Justice, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  January